{
    "subject": "Masud_Ahmad",
    "predicate": "worksAt",
    "object": "Pakistan_Atomic_Energy_Commission",
    "human_readable": "Masud Ahmad works at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9862696528434753,
            "question": "What kind of work might Masud Ahmad do at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8304799199104309,
            "question": "Does Masud Ahmad's job involve nuclear energy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7416656613349915,
            "question": "Where does Masud Ahmad work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6160711646080017,
            "question": "Is Masud Ahmad employed at a scientific institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765793323516846,
            "question": "What country is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5622703433036804,
            "question": "What type of organization is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5183408856391907,
            "question": "Is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission a well-known institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5011376142501831,
            "question": "Could Masud Ahmad's work contribute to scientific advancements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4090259373188019,
            "question": "Can you name any other organizations similar to the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4071769714355469,
            "question": "What is the name of Masud Ahmad's workplace?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Masud Ahmad works at the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission.",
            "html": "yago_17546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other organizations similar to the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?",
            "html": "yago_17546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Masud Ahmad's work contribute to scientific advancements?",
            "html": "yago_17546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission a well-known institution?",
            "html": "yago_17546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17546_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Dr. Masud Ahmad's association with the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission (PAEC). Specifically, Document 40.txt mentions his role as a \"former Member Science in Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission (PAEC)\" and details his involvement in the Theoretical Physics Group within PAEC."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}